我感觉很好  嗑药也得到了控制
I feel great,and the pills are under control.
一切都在掌控之中
Everything's under control.
你在超市暴力袭击一位男士
Is it true that you violently
这件事是真的吗
assaulted a man in a supermarket?
小鲍开始对我们玩阴的了
Bob Little has found a way to go negative.
我们人气现在急转直下
We're down to the wire.
他会把这两百分点的领先优势扩大到五点
He can turn this two-point lead to a five-point lead.
支持率下降了四个百分点
Dropped four points.
我们建议让他在剩下的学年内
We're recommending that he move back to the fourth grade
会到四年级念书
for the rest of the year.
我很遗憾  茱莉亚
I'm sorry, Julia.
没人让你辞掉工作
No one asked you to go quit your job.
就跟没人让你私下去找明基朵老师一样
Just like you went and talked to Miss Mikindoe.
这不公平
This isn't fair.
难道我要跟西德妮念同一个年级吗
Then I'll be in the same grade as Sydney?
那我的朋友呢
And what about all my friends?
你做得到的
You can do this.
你是个勇敢的男子汉
You're a brave boy.
好了
All right.
- 嘿  维克多  - 干嘛
- Hey, Victor. - What's up?
怎么啦  维克多
What's up, Victor?
老兄  我听说他挂科了
Dude, I heard he flunked.
看那边
Ah, look there.
你做得到的  儿子
You can do this, buddy.
我们会帮你另找一个学校的
You know what,we're gonna take a second.
走吧
Come on.
先去上个厕所
Let's go to the bathroom.
嘿  茱莉亚  怎么了
Hey, Julia, what's up?
- 嘿  - 出什么事了
- Hey. - What's happening?
哦...你知道就那事儿...
Oh, you know...
- 你还好吗  - 还行
- You all right? - Yeah.
嗯...
Um...
今天维克多要换班级了
Today's the day that Victor's changing classrooms.
- 对此我很遗憾   - 没关系的
- I'm sorry. - It's okay.
他要留级到四年级了
He's going down to fourth.
- 对啊  - 我不是说留级那个意思...
- Yeah. - I didn't mean down to--
转到四..对  随便啦
over to--yeah, whatever,
反正都是到四年级
into fourth.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
听着  我知道这对你来说很难受  但是...
Look, I know it's hard, but...
但这样做对他最好
It's the best thing for him.
他得待在他该待的地方
You know,he's got to be where he needs to be.
对
Yeah.
眼光要放长远
In the long run, you know.
- 对  - 我很抱歉
- Yeah. - I'm sorry.
- 哦~ 嘿  - 呃~ 你还记得艾德吧
- Oh, hey. - Oh, you remember ed?
艾德  当然记得  你好
Ed, yeah, hey.
- 嗨  乔  - 呃...
- Hi, Joel. - Uh...
我们得送这小子去教室了
We got to get this guy to class.
当然...  不好意思
Yeah, sorry.
好吧
Okay.
你坐到我的位子上了
You're in my seat.
- 我才没有  - 没错  你现在就坐在我的位子上
- No, I'm not. - Yes, actually, you are.
这是我的椅子
This is my chair,
还有这张是我的书桌  这些都是我的东西
this is my desk, and, like, all my stuff.
这是我老爸的店
My dad owns this whole place.
你爸是汉克吗
Your dad is Hank?
对  我爸就是汉克
Yes, my dad is Hank.
所以这些都是我的东西
Which means all this stuff is mine.
这些都无所谓
It doesn't matter.
可是你还是坐到我的位子上了  而且我现在很忙
You're still in my seat,and I'm swamped.
随你便吧
Whatever.
你移动过我的椅子了
And you moved my chair.
那你是谁  奴役还是什么
So what are you, slave labor or something?
不是  奴隶是违法的
No, slaves are illegal.
那你到底是什么
What are you then?
我现在没工夫跟你闲聊
I don't have time to talk right now.
我还有两卷胶片要冲洗
I still have two rolls of film to develop,
而且刚才57路公车还晚点了
and the 57 bus was late,
可能是因为大学街那边堵住了
possibly due to traffic on College Avenue.
有时候交通堵塞
Sometimes the traffic gets blocked up,
会影响公车的时刻表
and it affects the bus schedule.
公车时刻表一点也不精确  一点也不
Bus schedules are not precise.Far from it.
所以我来这儿晚了十分钟
So now I'm ten minutes late,
而你又耽搁了我另外五分钟时间
and you just wasted another five.
你们俩见过面了对吧
Hey, you guys met, huh?
- 露比  这是麦克斯  - 嗯哼
- Ruby, that's Max. - Mmhmm.
她重新动过我书桌的布局了
She rearranged the stuff on my desk.
他在学习摄影  而且干得非常不错
He's learning photography.He's pretty good.
我去外边买个油炸圈  好吗
Well, I'm going out for a doughnut, okay?
什么  不  不行  等等  等等
What? No, no, hold on. Hold on.
你要是要出去买油炸圈
If you're going to get doughnuts,
那就该先问问
then you should probably find out
还有没有其他人要油炸圈  知道吗
if any of us wants some doughnuts, hmm?
- 你想要油炸圈吗  - 废话
- You want a doughnut? - Sure.
好极了
Great.
- 拜  - 拜
- Bye. - Bye.
- 再给我带俩果冻  - 果冻恶心死了
- Couple jelly. - Jelly's gross.
你见过露比了  对吧
So you met Ruby, huh?
她得花一段时间才能混熟  但是...
She takes a little while to warm up, but...
她多大了
How old is she?
十四岁
14.
十四  很好
14. Perfect.
走吧  我们迟到了不少时间
Let's go, all right? We're late.
- 我们今天得把这个弄完  - 我知道
- We got to get this done. - Yeah, I know.
我迟到了十分钟因为
I was ten minutes late because the bus
- 57路公交车晚点了...  - 嗯  我刚才都听到了
- on 57 was delayed due to..- Yeah,I heard,I heard
非常感谢
Thank you so much.
明天就是选举日了  我现在参选
Election day is tomorrow.I'm running.
我是克里斯蒂娜・布雷弗曼  为了更好
I'm Kristina Braverman, for a better
的贝克里而奋斗  非常感谢
braver Berkeley.Thank you so much.
多谢  嗨  各位  你们还好吗
Thank you.Hi, guys. How are you?
我能给你一张保险杆贴纸吗
Can I give you a bumper sticker?
她要竞选下一位市长  记得告诉你父母...
She's gonna be the next mayor.Tell your parents...
真可爱  你好~
cute! Hi!
好了  东西齐了  你们都要哪个
All right, soup's on. Who got what?
好吧  吃好啊
All righty. Enjoy.
这是实打实的全有机肉
You got 100% organic ground chuck.
你们要用来怎么来配菜呢
What are you gonna make with that?
好了  来照张相
Okay, take a picture.
谢谢  真是很有趣呢
Thank you. That was fun.
【孩子们在大喊大叫】
[Kids yelling]
耶
Yay.
- 随时都可以打给我  - 非常感谢
- Call me anytime to discuss.- Thank you so much.
我把电话留给你
I'm gonna give you my phone number.
- 谢谢  - 祝你竞选好运
- Thank you very much.- Good luck on the campaign.
对  这就是我竞选的理由
Yes, and that is why I'm running.
我想为你们而战
I want to fight for you.
所以一定要让我赢得这场选举哦  周二来投票  好吗
So let's win this election. Vote Tuesday, okay?
- 喔哦~  - 喔哦~
- Whoo! - Whoo!
早餐我请了
Breakfast is on me.
不行
No.
吃华夫饼吗
Waffles?
每位家长都在这儿
Every parent in there.
- 这些孩子真是太可爱了  - 克里斯蒂娜・布雷弗曼
-And those kids were so cute.-Kristina Braverman?
你没看到这些家长的表情吗
But did you see the parents' faces?
他们...
They were like--
- 嗨  - 嗨  你好吗
- Hi. - Hi, how are you?
我在投你的票呢  祝你好运啊
I'm voting for you, so good luck.
非常感谢  你能这样做真是太好了
Oh, thank you so much.That's really nice of you.
- 你怀孕了吗  - 对啊  五个月了
- Oh, are you pregnant? - Yes, five months.
- 男孩还是女孩  - 女孩
- What are you having? - A little girl.
克里斯蒂娜  我有东西给你看
Kristina, let me show you something.
你现在很忙吧  祝你好运了
I know you're busy. Good luck.
好吧  谢谢  小心点啊
Okay, thank you. Take care.
- 她人太好了  - 看这个
- She was so sweet. - Look at this.
新的民意统计数据出来了  我们只落后两点五个百分点了
The new polls came in.We're within 2 1/2 points.
我们做得到的
We could do this.
我能赢的
I could win.
- 我们现在有事儿做了  - 好吧
- We got work to do. - Okay.
为人父母
? May God bless and keep you always
? and may your wishes all come true
? may you always do for others
? and let others do for you
? may you build a ladder to the stars
? and climb on every rung
? and may you stay
? forever young
? may you grow up to be righteous
? may you grow up to be true ?
? may you always know the truth
? and see the lights surrounding you
? may you always be courageous
? stand upright and be strong
? and may you stay
? forever young
? may you stay
第五季第九集
幕雨字幕组译制
翻译：Brynt&超威闫叔  校订：Brynt&超威闫叔
时间轴：花格子神尼&拜仁小攀  后期：Brynt
- 请为克里斯蒂娜・布雷弗曼投票  - 嗨  你好
- Vote for Kristina Braverman. - Hi, there.
- 不用了  - 要克里斯蒂娜・布雷弗曼头像的别针吗
- No. - Kristina Braverman pin?
我了解克里斯蒂娜  她是一位
I know Kristina, and she is someone
真真正正可以代表您跟您家人意愿的人
who would truly represent you and your family.
- 她聪明  诚实...  - 嗨  大家好
- She's smart, she's honest, - Hey, guys.
要克里斯蒂娜・布雷弗曼别针吗  为了竞选市长来着
Kristina Braverman pin? For mayor?
所以请你明天一定出门为她投上一票
So please get out and vote tomorrow.
- 我绝对会去的  - 我们需要您的一票
- Oh, I will. - We need it.
而且我会拖上我那个整天宅在家的懒鬼老公一起去
And I'll bring my lazy-ass husband with me,too.
那谢谢啦  我们一样也需要他的一票
Thank you. We need his vote too.
你真是神了...看看你
You're magic at--look at you.
- 怎么啦  - 我一个都送不出去
- What? - I cannot give these away.
我觉得我连五美元的钞票都送不出去
I don't think I could give away a $5 bill.
太棒了  我爱死这份差事了
Well, this is great. I'm loving this.
对  你完全秒杀众人了
Yeah, you're killing it.
给你一份  请为克里斯蒂娜投上你关键的一票
Here you go, vote for Kristina.
我不想再宣传了
I don't want to instigate,
你却一点也不觉得被冒犯了吗
but you're not offended by this, are you?
没有啊  为什么这么说
No, why?
克里斯蒂娜跟海瑟把我们
Well, the fact that Kristina and Heather
派到这里来
sent us here, you know.
你是她们认识的唯一一个黑人
I mean, you're the only black person they know,
所以她们派你来黑人社区
and they sent you to the black neighborhood.
- 我就是觉得  - 才不是呢  你怎么会这样想
- I just think-- - No, why-
反正我是觉得有点不爽
Well, I'm kind of offended for you.
别这样
Don't be.
我是一个名誉上的黑人
I mean, and I'm an honorary black person,
- 所以我觉得有点不爽  - 亲爱的  你其实非常
- so I'm a little offended. - Honey, you are very
- 非常白人呢  - 喔哦  在这个范围之内
- very white. - Whoa, on the spectrum,
左右分别是黑人跟白人  亚当在右边
right, of black and white,Adam's here.
- 菲尔科汉在左边  - 那你呢
- Farrakhan's here. - And where are you?
我就在中间  我就在四分之三的...
I'm right here. I'm like 3/4 of the way to--
我觉得要是你这样想  在这个范围之内
Well, I guess if you put it that way, on that spectrum,
跟你哥哥相比  你不如他白
as opposed to your brother, you are not as white as him.
既然你不觉得被冒犯的话...
As long as you're not offended...
- 但你还是非常白的  - 那我就...
- But you're still very white. - Then I'm...
不  亲爱的  我真没这么觉得  我真很享受这个过程
No, baby, I'm really not. I'm really into this.
选角以及被选举
You know, elections and voting,
对我来说真的有很重大的意义
it really means a lot to me.
零八年我把票投给了奥巴马
I mean, casting my ballot for Obama in '08
是我这一生中做过的最有意义的事儿了
was one of the most meaningful things I've ever done.
你想想  我们经历了那么多困难
You know,like,thinking about how far we've come,
我还帮助选举了史上第一位黑人总统
and that I helped to elect the first black president.
我从未想过这件事会在我活着的时候发生
I mean, I never thought that
would happen in my lifetime.
我知道你很难把这两件事联系在一起
I mean,I know you can't really relate to that,
- 但是...-  我当然可以
- but. - Yeah, I can.
- 真的吗  - 绝对可以
- Really? - Totally.
我不认为这是肤色问题
I don't think that was a black-white thing.
这真的是我所了解的意义深远的
I mean, it was really a profound moment
- 时刻  - 确实是
- I got-- - It was.
对  当我投票的时候  我情绪非常激动
Yeah, when I voted, I got emotional.
- 我还哭了呢  - 是吗
I cried. - You did?
- 对  我哭了  - 我都不知道诶
- Yeah,I cried--yeah. - I didn't know that,aw.
哭的跟个孩子似的
Like a baby.
还记得你第一次得到小贴纸的时候吗
Remember when you got your Little sticker?
当然记得  我现在还留着呢
Yeah, I still have it someplace.
- 是吗  - 当然  我觉得应该还在
- You do? - Yeah, I think so.
- 我也还留着呢  - 是吗
- So do I. - Yeah?
哦~~
Aw.
你最好了
You're the best.
我爱死你了
I love you.
好了  你想让其显像的部分
Okay,so the area that you want to bring out more,
你就打开灯光  把那个部分放在这个小洞上
you let the light on through
the hole just a little more.
你只需要盯着就行
You just go over it.
所以要是我们想让栅栏显像出来的话
So we want that fence to come out.
就往上抬一点  来  你来试试
So we just go up. Here, you try it.
只需要让光线透过栅栏
We just want that light on that fence.
好了
All right.
我想让露比做我女朋友
I have intentions of asking Ruby to be my girlfriend.
什么
What?
你作为父亲  我觉得应该让你知道
As the father,I thought you should know.
我...等..等...不行  麦克斯  呃...
I mean--ho, ho, no, Max, uh...
这样做可不太好
That's not a good idea.
- 为什么不好  - 因为她是我女儿
- Why not? - 'Cause she's my daughter.
我知道  要不是这样我们还遇不到呢
I know. That's how we met.
那你为什么想让她做你女朋友
Why do you even want her as a girlfriend anyway?
她穿着鲨鱼衫
She was wearing a sharks shirt.
- 没错  - 而我是鲨鱼粉
- Yeah. - I'm a sharks fan.
这就说明我们有共同爱好
That means we have common interests.
更何况我们年纪相仿  我是男生  她又是女生
Also,we're both 14,and I'm a boy,and she's a girl,
这就说明她符合所有条件
which means she meets all the requirements.
麦克斯  别这样
You know, Max, come on.
首先  她生活在明尼苏达州
First of all, she lives in Minnesota.
而且她很喜怒无常  你已经见识过了  不是吗
She's moody.You saw what she's like,right?
我明天就问她
I'm asking her tomorrow.
嘿  你在这儿干嘛呢
Hey,what are you doing up here?
你觉得我看起来是在干嘛
What does it look like?
看起来你好像是在
Well, it looks like you're profiling
素描一个连环杀手之类的东西
a serial killer or something.
你现在在联邦调查局找到工作了吗
Have you taken a job with the FBI?
可能吧  机缘巧合...  我也不清楚
Maybe, by accident, I don't know.
太糟糕了  这到底是个什么样的体制啊
This is terrible.What kind of system is this?
- 我都搞晕了  - 这是你亚当舅舅弄的
- I'm so confused. - Oh, this is your Uncle Adam.
他喜欢那些旧玩意儿
He loves anything antiquated.
纸啊  蒸汽机啊
Paper, steam engines.
- 要是他能骑一匹马  - 我真的很喜欢...
- if he could ride  - I would really love to...
来上班的话  他肯定会这样做的
a horse to work, he would.
这玩意儿太糟了  我们得设法越过去
It's really bad.We should try to move past this.
你很忙对吧
Well, you're busy.
我本来打算让你下楼来帮我
I was gonna ask you to help me downstairs
做一些有创造性有艺术气息和音乐感的事儿的
with something creative and artistic and musical,
- 但看样子你是不会有兴趣了 - 什么
- but that wouldn't interest you. - What?
- 这件事看样子...  - 你在说什么呢
-The case seems to be -What are you talking about?
现在很热的  所以我先希望你能找到你要找的罪犯
Hot right now, so I hope you find your man.
克罗斯比  等等
Crosby! Wait!
现在情况是这样的
Here's what's happening.
明天我们会有一个后备歌手来录音
Tomorrow we have backup vocalists coming in to record.
好吧  所以呢
Okay, so?
我们需要临时音轨
We need a scratch track,
这就需要你来加入了
and that's where you come in.
- 你要来唱临时音轨  - 什么
- You are going to sing said scratch track.- What?
不  克罗斯比  不不不不
No, Crosby, no, no, no, no, no.
- 没错  就是要你来唱  - 不  我还没准备好呢
- Yes, you are. - No, 'cause I'm not ready.
机会可不是每天都有的  所以你还是先唱吧
Opportunities do not come every day, so please.
唱什么  唱《带你回家》吗
For what, for taking you home?
我没有...我不...不不不不
I don't have--I'm not--no, no, no, no, no.
你了解这首歌  是也不是
Hey, you know the song or not?
- 没错  你了解  - 我是了解  但我还没准备好
- Yes, you do. - I know it, but I'm not ready.
我得先开开声之类的
I have to get my voice warmed up and stuff.
你们早就准备好了是不是
You're gonna be in here for this?
玩真的吗
Really?
好了  开始了
Okay, here we go.
【音乐声起】
[Music begins]
【清嗓子】
[Clears throat]
? 难道我不愿意再次抓住你
? Wouldn't I love to hold you again
? 我们醉得如此厉害
? we were so messed up and busy
? 还忙着将它留在你的眼中
? with keeping it in your eyes
? 我们象征着
? we're standing for something
? 一些我们看不见的东西
? that I couldn't see
? 但我知道它已在路上
? but I knew it was coming
? 我们只是在迷恋
? we're just one crush away
? 我依然想要你更多
? I still want you more
? 我们无法整天都躺在这儿
? we could lay here all day
? 我依然想要你更多
? I'd still want you more
? 更多  更多
? more, more
? 我本该带你回家
? I should have taken you home
? 带你回家
? taken you home
- 嗨  - 嘿
- Hi. - Hey.
不好意思回来晚了
Sorry it's kind of late.
- 没错  - 嘿  亲爱的
- Yep. - Hey, bud.
天呐  今天真是太美好了
Oh, my gosh, it's such a good day.
你过得怎么样
How's it going?
- 很好  - 很好吗  那就好
- Good. - Good. Great.
我做了晚饭  但是...
I got dinner for us but I...
- 没关系的  - 我已经吃过了
- Oh, that's okay. - I already ate it.
- 你可以加热后再吃  - 没关系的
- You can heat it up. - That's okay.
我其实还不怎么饿
I'm actually not that hungry anyway.
天呐  我今天过得真是太棒了
God, I had such a good day.
我今天给乐队录了一段临时音轨
I recorded a guide vocal track today with the band.
- 不错  - 对啊  你能相信吗
- Cool. - Yeah, can you believe it?
听起来不错
That sounds cool.
我真的紧张死了
And I was really nervous,
因为  我...
because, I was, like,
不得不在那群男生面前唱
having to sing in front of those boys,
但效果其实还是相当不错
but it actually went really, really well.
肯定的
Of course.
所以  还算不错了
So, I don't know, it was good.
我...我也不好说啦
I mean, I don't know.
你呢  今天过得怎么样
So how about you? How was your day?
挺好的  我下班回家挺早的
It was good, I got home early so
所以我点了你最喜欢吃的
I ordered your favorite, you know,
本来想来个浪漫的晚餐的
and I just,I thought we'd have a romantic dinner,
但我不知道你会回来的这么晚
but I didn't know you were going
to be getting home so late.
你生我气了吗
Are you mad at me?
没有  就是有点不高兴
No, I'm just bummed.
我点了食物还准备好了一切
You know, I got all that food and everything.
不是因为那些
No, not about that.
我感觉好像自从我们处理了戒指之后...
I feel like ever since we dealt with the ring...
- 没有的事  - 我不知道
- No! - I don't know,
- 感觉就好像我们有了距离感  - 不  跟戒指
- like a little distant or-- - No, there's nothing
没有关系  我们已经处理好了那件事儿了
about the ring.We've already dealt with that.
- 现在没事儿了  就...  - 我知道 但我...
- It's fine now, it's-- - I know, but I just-
但我觉得你觉得我
it feels like you took it really personally,
- 根本不喜欢它一样  - 它根本不值得留在我们脑中
- like I didn't like it.- It's not worth in our minds.
不  它根本就不值得来谈
No, it's not even worth talking about.
我很高兴  这样做很好  我就是想你了而已
I'm happy.It's great.I just missed you, that's all.
我只是想你了
I just miss you.
好吧
Okay.
- 我没生气  - 好吧  好吧
- I'm not mad. - Okay, okay.
- 我向你保证  - 好吧
- I promise. - Okay.
我保证
I promise.
好吧
Okay.
我真的好想你
I just really missed you,you know.
- 我也很想你  - 嗯哼
- I missed you too. - Mm-hmm.
- 嘿  - 干嘛
- Hey. - What?
还有一件事
There was one other thing
我想跟你速战速决
I wanted to talk to you about real fast.
- 什么事  - 等等
- What? - Wait, wait.
怎么啦
What?
你又在吃那些药了吗
Are you taking those pills again?
什么药
What?
我之前洗衣服的时候
I was doing laundry,
我去拿你的衣服来洗
and I was putting some of your stuff away,babe,
然后就在你包里发现了那些玩意儿
and I saw that they were in there,
然后我...
and I just--
我没有
no.
那是个...是个老方子了
That's a--I mean,that's an old prescription.
但我实在两周前发现的
Well, it's from two weeks ago.
我知道  我...我...我没有...
Yeah, I know.I-I-I haven't--
他们没停止  但我...
they haven't stopped it, but I--
那是之前的老方子了
it's an old prescription from before.
我甚至都没需要过它
I don't even need it.
那些事抗焦虑药...
Those are anxiety pills that are--
亲爱的  你吃不吃其实无所谓的
babe,I--it doesn't bother me if you take them,
我真没吃过
I just--I'm not taking them.
- 好吧 好吧  - 我根本就不需要
- Okay, okay. - I don't even need them.
我只是想...那让我感觉你好像在瞒着我什么事
I just wanted--it felt like you were hiding it from me,
- 我想让你知道你没有必要隐瞒我  - 没有
- and I want you to know you don't have to. - No.
不不不  我没有隐瞒你任何事
No, no, I'm not hiding anything from you.
我只是不想让你因此紧张或是害怕
I just didn't want you to be nervous or freak out about it.
好吧
Okay.
我爱你
I love you.
? 最后一次尝试
? One last try
【手机铃声响了】
[cell phone chimes]
我希望他能睡得着叫
I hope he can sleep.
嗯  那天现在怎么样
Yeah, how was he?
一直在强忍着
Stoic.
你有条艾德・布鲁克斯的短信
You got a text from Ed Brooks.
哦
Oh.
你们俩好像最近短信来往不少嘛
You guys have been texting each other a lot lately.
对  责任委员会那些破事儿
Yeah, sustainability committee
简直占据了我的所有时间
is taking over my life.
想喝茶吗
Do you want some tea?
不想
Nope.
我很好
I'm good.
你们必须得投票吗
Do you have to vote?
你是没有责任  但你有义务这样做
You don't have to, but you should.
这是作为一个民主国家的公民
You know,it's your civic responsibility,
应尽的义务
living in a democracy, which we live in,
这是建立政府的最伟大之处
which is the greatest form of government,
应为你可以告诉他们你自己的想法
'cause you can tell them what your opinion is.
走吧  去帮你的伯母
Let's go ahead, and make your aunt
竞选成为这座美丽城市的市长吧
the mayor of this fine city.
- 对  - 你好  伊迪
- Yeah. - Hello there, Edie.
早上好
Good morning.
选民投票情况如何
How's voter turnout?
在我看来还是他们还是蛮热衷于这事儿的
Looks pretty strong to me.
挺热衷的
Pretty strong.
对议员强烈的喜爱
Pretty strong favors our candidate.
- 说的不错  - 对
- Well, good for you.- Yeah.
我们要投给克里斯蒂娜・布雷弗曼
Our candidate is Kristina Braverman.
她是个非常帮的候选人
She's a heck of a candidate.
你是布雷弗曼的支持者吗
Are you a Braverman supporter?
我们这的不能讨论这个
We're really not supposed to talk about this.
名字  谢谢
Name, please.
- 克罗斯比・布雷弗曼  - 布雷弗曼
- Crosby Braverman. - Braverman.
就跟候选人克里斯蒂娜・布雷弗曼一个姓
Just like the candidate, Kristina Braverman.
我没在名单上看到你的名字
I don't see your name on our list.
你确定你是这个选区的吗
Are you sure this is your polling place?
我就住在那条街  所以我...
Well, I live right up the street, so I--
你应该有张印着你的
well, you should have gotten a postcard
选区的明信片
with your polling place on it.
对  但肯定是这个地方
Right,this would have to be the place.
这里离我家这么近
It's so close to my house.
你作为选民已经多久了
How long has it been since you voted?
跟这没什么关系吧
That's not entirely relevant.
是不是有张表格我需要填
If there's a form or something I've got to fill out
选民注册表
the voter registration form.
但是你不能在选举这天去注册
You can't register to vote the day of the election.
为什么不能
Why not?
因为这样行不通
Because it doesn't work that way.
好了  听我说
Okay, listen to me.
我可算是美国遵纪守法的纳税好公民
I am an American citizen who pay my taxes.
我父亲是一名越战老兵  而且布雷弗曼家族...
My father is a Vietnam vet,and the Bravermans--
先生  你现在让后面的人排起了长队
sir, now you are holding up the line.
我只是...投给克里斯蒂娜・布雷弗曼
I'm just--Kristina Braverman.
是不是还有其他办法
If there's another way
可以解决这事儿  我需要投票
for me to sort this out,I need to vote.
我需要你离开
And I need you to leave.
你没在这儿注册
You are not registered here.
但是我们不是要进去
But don't we get to go inside
按下所有的按钮吗
and push all the buttons?
听着  我本来打算悄悄投票的
Listen,okay,you know what,I wanted to vote privately,
但她现在要求我公开投票
but now she has forced us
说这样更好
to vote publicly,which is fine.
我们要公开投票
We'll vote publicly.
所以  我  克罗斯比・布雷弗曼
So I, Crosby braverman,
要为克里斯蒂娜・布雷弗曼成为市长
vote for Kristina braverman
- 投上一票  - 我也是
- for mayor. - Me too.
我们公开投票
We voted publicly.
你们各位要见证这一切
You guys witnessed it.
记下来  我们等她赢的时候再见
Mark it down,and we'll see you when she wins.
你愿意做我女朋友吗
So do you want to be my girlfriend?
什么
What?
你愿意做我的女朋友吗
Do you want to be my girlfriend?
嗯...
Um...
不可能
Not gonna happen.
为什么
Why?
不好意思  我现在有事要做
Excuse me,I'm doing something.
嘿  露比  你能过来一下吗
Hey, Ruby, come here for a second please.
干嘛
What?
对他好点儿
Just be, like, nicer to him.
- 好吗  - 什么
- All right? - What?
就麦克斯  你放他一马吧
Just Max. Just cut him a break.
你在说什么呢  他是那个...
What are you talking about?He's the one--
我只是让你稍微对他好一点儿而已
I'm just saying be a little bit nicer,that's all.
那我是要当他女朋友吗
So be his girlfriend?
不是  我不是那个意思
No, I'm not saying that.
听着  他不会有任何实际行动的
Look, he's not gonna do anything.
他也只是这么说说而已
He just wants to say he has a girlfriend,that's all.
这是男人之间的事儿
It's a guy thing.
你要回到明尼苏达的对吧
I mean, you're gonna be in Minnesota, right?
所以这么做做又有何妨呢
So what's the harm really?
别...拜托
Oh, don't--come on.
我不能相信你
I can't believe you.
好了 露比
All right, Ruby.
我要给老妈打电话
I'm calling mom.
别跟你妈打电话
Do not call mom.
别打给你吗  拜~
Don't call mom. Bye.
【布鲁斯音乐演奏中】
[Bluesy music playing]
- 维克多刚才摔门了  - 我知道
- Victor slammed the door. - I know.
他还在车上说了S打头那词
And he said the "s" word in the car.
我知道
I know.
- 所以他没有甜点吃了 对吧  - 我不知道
- So no dessert, right? - I don't know.
- 这是规定  - 西德妮
- Well, that's the rules. - Sydney.
嘿  小家伙  听着
Hey, buddy, listen--
维克多  你干嘛呢
Victor,what are you doing?
闭上你丫的臭嘴  西德妮
Shut the hell up,Sydney.
- 维克多  - 老妈  你听到他刚才说什么了吗
- Victor.- Mom,did you just hear what he just said
维克多  马上给我停下
Victor, stop right now.
西德妮 去你的房间  马上
Sydney, go to your room right now.
- 这不公平  - 西德妮  回你的房间去
- That's so unfair. - Sydney, go to your room,
这样我就可以跟你哥哥好好谈谈
so I can talk to your brother.
- 维克多 过来好吗  - 我恨你
-Victor,come here please-I hate you.
- 这太不公平了  - 你能回来吗
- This is so unfair! - Can you come back here?
- 你甚至都不...  - 好吧
- You don't even-- - Okay.
嘿  我知道你现在很难受
Hey.I know this is hard for you,
但是这样对你是最好的
but it's the best thing for you.
为什么  是因为我是个吊车尾吗
Why, because I'm a 'tard?
不是
No.
不许用那个词说自己  好吗
Don't use that word about yourself, okay?
- 也不许那样说别人  - 为什么不行
- or about anybody. - Why not?
- 这是事实  - 这不是  维克多
- It's true. - It's not true, Victor.
伊桑跟他那帮狐朋狗友都这么说
Well, Ethan and his asshat friends said it,
所以一定是这样的
so it must be true.
伊桑这么说的  我会告诉学校的
Ethan said that?I will talk to the school.
- 我会跟他妈妈谈的  - 这样只会让事情更糟
- I'll talk to his mother... - That will just make it worse.
听着  我知道你现在不好过  但是...
Listen,I know this is rough,buddy,but this is--
这样是最好的  我知道  茱莉亚
it's for the best. I know, Julia.
你都跟我说了千八十遍了
You said it a million times.
我们能谈谈这个吗
Can we talk about this, buddy?
为什么当我是个笨蛋的时候你却说我很聪明
Why did you say I was smart,when I'm dumb?
宝贝
Sweetheart...
你就是个大骗子
You're a liar.
嘿  能先停会儿吗
Hey, can you stop?
可以
Yeah.
因为我想对你忏悔...
'Cause I want to confess to you that...
我之前并不想你来竞选
I didn't want you to do this.
我认为你在癌症之后
I didn't think you were ready to handle
控制不住你的压力  但你...
the stress after cancer,but you...
你已经准备好了
You were ready,
不管输赢  我都为你而骄傲
and I am so proud of you, win or lose.
克里斯蒂娜  我真为你骄傲
Kristina, I'm so proud of you.
- 谢谢  - 这一切都太疯狂了
- Thanks. - It's crazy.
我知道 但我真的先要这样
I know. I really want this.
我知道
I know.
【民乐演奏中】
[Gentle ballad playing]
谁啊
Who is it?
嘿
Hey.
- 你好  - 啊
- Hello. - Aah!
- 天呐  - 你说了请进的
- Oh, my God! - You said come in.
你怎么进来的
How did you get in here?
你难道没说请进吗
Didn't you say come in?
没有  我说了“谁啊”
No, I said, "who is it?"
门是开着的
Oh, the door was open.
听着  我现在需要一个女人
Listen, I need a woman, now.
啊~
Uh
我女儿来我这儿住两天  所以你不用紧张
my daughter's here for a couple of days,so relax.
哦
Oh.
简直是个灾难
And it's a disaster.
眼泪都快给我急出来了
Tears have been shed.
东西也被扔出来了
Stuff has been thrown.
为什么  出什么事了
Why, what happened?
麦克斯想让她做他的女朋友
Max asked her to be his girlfriend.
他俩在一起会很开心的
Well, they'll be very happy together.
她可是个辣妹
She's a hottie.
你开玩笑呢  说真的  这...
Trying to be funny? Really? Just--
听着  我知道  我知道这确实让你压力山大
Listen,I know.I'm sure it's very stressful.
你得告诉他们做好保护措施
Just tell them they have to use protection.
我来这儿是想寻求你的建议的
You know,I come here for advice--
有什么问题吗  我没觉着有什么不好啊
Well, what happened?I don't get what's wrong.
哪里有问题吗  她还没准备好这一切
What's wrong? She's not ready for this.
麦克斯也没有
And Max doesn't, you know,
他甚至都不知道自己为什么要个女朋友
he doesn't even know why he wants a girlfriend.
他只是在照章办事
He's just checking stuff off a list.
你还没准备好这一切吗
You're not ready for this.
她已经十四了  马上就要成年了
She's 14 and,you know,it's right around the corner.
她还没准备好  没准备好  好吗
She's not ready. She's not ready, okay?
- 好吧  - 顺便提一句
- Okay. - And by the way,
她觉得麦克斯很怪
she thinks he's weird, you know.
他当然会这么觉得
Of course she does,
但你对她怎么说的
but what did you say to her?
她...
She just, you know,
她认为我要把她
she thinks I'm trying to sell her
买去当妓女之类的
into prostitution or something.
天呐  你到底对她说什么了
Oh, my God.What did you say to her?
我告诉她  为什么她不能
I told her, why doesn't she just
假装是麦克斯的女朋友呢
pretend to be his girlfriend,
反正她不久就会回明尼苏达州
because she's going to Minnesota.
- 天呐  - 她立马就掉头走开了
- Oh, my God. - She's going away.
又没有什么坏处  没什么大碍
There's no harm. There's no foul.
- 他又不会知道  - 这真是最糟的建议了
- He doesn't know. - That's the worst advice,
她当然会生气咯
of course she's upset.
你让她跟麦克斯撒谎
You told her to lie to Max.
是对他好点  不是撒谎  是对他好一点
To be nice, not lie.Just be nice.
这不是在让她对他好
That's not being nice though.
这是在叫她撒谎
It teaches her that you lie
以便自己能脱身于一个奇怪的处境
to get out of a tricky situation,
而且   对他来说
and anyway, for him, you know,
他得自己去搞懂
he's gonna have to figure out,
并不是你说喜欢她那个女孩就得当你女朋友
you don't have a girlfriend just
because you say you like her.
她也得喜欢你才行  这是双边的关系
She has to like you back.It's a two-way street.
你说得对
Oh, you're right.
女孩太难伺候了
Oh, girls are the worst.
什么
Huh?
我说  谢谢你
I said thanks, yeah.
- 好吧  - 你说得对
- Okay. - Yeah, you're right.
好吧
All right.
你真该把门锁上  知道吗
You should really lock this,okay?
这一带有些奇怪的家伙  我还看见了一只丛林狼
There's a weird guy. I saw a coyote.
多谢提醒
Thanks.
嘿  还是我
Hey, it's me, again.
我知道我都给你打了五通电话了
I know I've called you like five times,
可是维克多今天真的不好过
but Victor's having a really rough day,
我也知道你很忙
and I know you're busy, but
但我今天也过得很糟
I'm having a really rough day,
我现在只想跟你聊聊
and I just wanted to talk to you,
要是你有时间的话
so, you know, if you get a chance,
要是你收到这条消息的话  请回我电话
if you get this message,please call me.
好吧  谢了
Okay, thanks.
唔~~
Ooh.
- 啊哈哈  - 耶
- Ah-ha-ha. - Yeah.
两个人也能玩这个游戏
Well, two can play at this game.
嘿
Hey.
你也得将我军
And you got to king me too, so...
- 嘿  - 嘿
- Hey. - Hey.
- 看看我给你带了什么  - 哇哦
- Look what I got for you. - Whoa!
真酷  谢谢
Cool, thanks.
现在只要你满了十八岁
Now when you're 18,
你也可以选举了
you'll get to vote too.
这是我们作为一个公民的最高荣誉
It's one of our greatest honors as citizens.
对  我知道  老爸跟我说过
Yeah, I know. Dad told me.
真的吗  真棒
Oh, really? Good.
肯定的  天佑美帝
You bet. God bless America.
- 没错  - 好了  那是个好动机
- That's right.- Okay, that's a good move.
等等  老妈  你想公开选举还是私下选举
Wait,mommy,did you vote public or private?
- 什么  - 哦哦~  我要走了
- What? - Uh-oh, here we go.
你要公开还是私人选举
Did you vote public or private?
我要走这个
I'm taking this guy.
什么是公开或私人选举
What's public or private?
老爸就是公开选举的
Well,daddy voted public.
- 他告诉桌子边的那位夫人  - 你在说什么呢
- He just told the lady - What are you talking?
- 他要投给谁票  - 哦
- at the table who he was voting for. - Oh.
- 那就是公开选举  - 哦
- That's voting public. - Oh.
而进去投票的人就是私下选举
The people that go into the booth are voting private.
这是不是跟你说的一样  老爸
Isn't that what you said, daddy?
我觉得你会有麻烦的
I think you're gonna get swamped here
要是你不...我是好像说过这话
if you don't-I may have said something like that.
听起来像..像...
Something that sounds like--something like--
你的招贴呢
where's your sticker?
对啊  你的招贴呢
Yeah, where's your sticker?
?我本该带你回家
?I should have taken you home
?yeah, I should have taken you home
?我本该带你回家
?I should have taken you home
?带你回家
?taken you home
?带你
?taken
?我本该带你
?I should have taken--
- 你说得没错  - 是的
- You're right. - Yes.
- 我们很棒  - 对
- We're good. - Yeah.
- 就像...  - 你确定
- Like... - Are you sure?
就别把钱花在什么后备歌手身上了
Let's not spend money on a back-up singer.
肯定呀
Absolutely.
因为这首听起来很棒  对吧
'Cause that sounds great, right?
- 她听起来太棒了  - 不好意思  什么
- Yeah, she sounds great.- I'm sorry, what?
你听起来太棒了
You sound good.
你是在说你要把这首歌
Wait,you're not saying you're gonna keep
收录到你们的专辑里面吗
that for your album?
- 真的吗  - 你是说真的
- Yes. - Are you serious?
- 哇哦  - 你是说真的吗
- Whoa-- - are you serious?
怎么...你们疯了吗
What the--you guys are crazy.
太感谢了
Thank you so much.
- 奥利弗  我的天呐  - 别谢我
- Oliver, oh, my God. - Don't thank me.
要谢就谢这家伙吧  是他推荐用你的
Thank he-man over here.He just got you in there.
听着  是金子总会发光的 对吧
Hey,look.When it's good it's good, right?
再录两首  我们就完工了
Two more songs,we got a record.
好了  现在能去喝酒了吗
Okay, so can we go drink now?
- 行  - 行啊
- Yeah. - Yeah.
走去酒吧吧
Let's go to the bar.
- 去移动酒吧  - 没错  老兄
- To the bar-mobile. - Yeah, man.
你去吗
You coming?
- 去酒吧吗  - 对
- To the bar? - Yes.
- 真的吗  - 走吧  你也去吧
- Really? - Come on, you're coming.
- 对  走吧  - 好吧
- Yeah, let's go. - Okay.
- 吃吧  柯尔克  - 是凯文啦
- Come on, kirk. - It's Kevin.
- 没关系啦   - 不好意思  吃个油炸圈吧
- I'm good. - Sorry. Have a doughnut.
吃一个吧  我们还有好多呢
Eat one. We've got a lot.
我是个波斯顿的卖冰淇淋的
I'm a Boston cream guy.
你要不吃的话  他会打你的
You never know,he might punch you.
- 我就吃一个  - 你已经见识过他有多暴力了
- I'm gonna take one.- You've seen how violent he is.
我来帮你们发吧
I'm gonna pass these out for you.
克里斯蒂娜  看看谁来了
Kristina, look who showed up.
嘿  些西恩
Hey.Thank you.
- 不客气  - 谢谢你
- You're welcome. - Thank you.
嗨 亲爱的  你还好吗
Hi, honey, how are you?
看看你
Look at you.
- 你看起来气色不错  - 谢谢
- You look good. - Thank you.
你知道你可以不在场投票的  你真是不要命了
You know you could have voted absentee,you ding-dong.
你不必跑这么大老远来的
You didn't have to come all the way out here.
只能想这一切吗
And miss all this?
没门儿
No way,
no way.
我现在很有可能
You know, there's a good chance
会输掉这场竞选  所以...
亲爱爱的  你已经赢了
Honey, you've already won.
我真为你而骄傲
I'm so proud of you.
真的
So proud of you.
很感谢你能来
Thank you for coming.
走去投票吧
Let's go vote.
对了  要是我投给小包的话没什么关系吧
Oh, is it a problem that I'm gonna vote for Bob Little?
【笑】
[Laughs]
- 这个办法不错  - 很棒
- That's a great fix. - Great.
那我们接下来要做的就是
And then, so all we need to do then, is we take the plumbing
通向二楼厨房的管道装置了
up through the kitchen to the second floor.
我们还可以加上厕所
And we can just add the toilets
- 之类的  - 对  我们做到了
- and all that stuff... - Yeah, we did it!
- 就在这儿  好了  - 很棒
- Right over there.Done. - Nice
你吃过鳗鱼吗  它太疯狂了  不是吗
Have you tried the eel,cause it's insane,isn't it?
我告诉你  它是从墙里的一个小洞里钻出来的
I'm telling you, it comes from this little hole in the wall.
这是海湾区最好吃的寿司了
It's the best Sushi in the bay area.
所以  要是我们...
So, if we have this--
- 嘿  - 嗨
- Hey. - Hi.
你来这干嘛呢
What are you doing here?
我能跟你谈谈吗
Can I talk to you?
孩子们呢  他们在...
Where are the kids?Are they--
他们在我父母家
they're at my parents'.
请你能跟我聊聊吗
Can I talk to you, please?
- 没什么急事  - 没人流血
- Nothing's an emergency.- Nobody's bleeding,
我想跟你谈谈  而且我跟你都打了五通电话了
but I would like to talk to you,and I've called you five times--
这是我的错  我一直都...
that's my fault,'cause I've been turning--
这跟你无关  皮特
you know,this is not about you, Peet.
- 茱莉亚  - 好吧  我...
- Julia. - Okay, I--
- 茱莉亚  - 我能跟你谈谈吗  请！！！
- Julia. - May I talk to you, please?
不用  你在这儿没关系的
No, no, you're fine.
没关系的  留在这儿
You're fine, please, stay.
茱莉亚  我现在在工作
Julia, I'm working right now,
我们回家再聊这件事
and we will talk about this when I get home.
我倒要看看你到底什么时候能回来
I'll see you whenever that is.
你是说你从来都没参过选
So you're saying you never voted, like, ever.
你这样说就太武断了
When you say it like that,it sounds very judgmental.
你不觉得应该换个不那么武断的方式来问吗
Do you think you could rephrase it in a less judgmental way?
我不觉得
I don't think I can.
你还有什么比零八年
What more important thing were you doing
为奥巴马投上一票更重要  你说啊
other than voting for Barack Obama in 2008, huh?
在选举期间我正在纳帕呢
I was incapacitated in Napa during that election.
在纳帕吗  纳帕  那你哭又是怎么一回事
Oh, Napa? Napa. What happened to crying?
你说你当时哭的像个孩子似的
You know, you said you cried like a baby.
你那天那么激动
You were getting very emotional,
还谈到你祖先之类的事儿
and you were talking about your ancestors and stuff...
我才没有呢
No, I wasn't.
我于是也有点身临其境了
And I got sucked up into it a little bit.
你还谈到了第十五次修正案
You were talking about the 15th Amendment...
- 我没有  - 还有说了公民权利之类的话
- No, I wasn't.- And civil rights stuff.
少废话  住口
Cut the crap.Cut the crap.
你甚至都不为你嫂子投票吗
You wouldn't even vote for your own sister-in-law?
- 你这人到底什么毛病  - 我试过了
- What's wrong with you? - I tried to.
- 那你怎么做的  - 我到那边之后
- How? - I went down there,
他们不让我进去
and they would not let me.
而我现在觉得  因为我们生活在一个民主国家
Now,I was assuming,because we live in a democracy,
我就能在投票当天注册  可是你猜怎么着
that I could register day of,and guess what?
我不能  这又不是我的错
I can't.It's not my fault.
我是一个遵纪守法的好公民  而且我真的已经尽力了
I am an upstanding citizen, and I tried.
要是她以一票之差落败
If she loses by one vote,
就全都怪你
which happens, it's your fault.
嘿  麦克斯
Hey, Max.
我想跟你聊会儿
Let me talk to you for a minute.
聊什么  我现在忙着呢
About what? I'm busy working.
你现在可以不忙工作
You don't got to work right now.
停一小会儿也无妨
Just stop for a second. It's okay.
这是我的地盘  对吧  所以我就是老板
It's my place, right, so I'm the boss.
我就想跟你谈谈露比的事儿
So I just want to talk to you about Ruby for a second.
她已经拒绝我让她当女朋友
She already said she doesn't want
的要求了  所以没什么可谈的
to be my girlfriend,so it's done.
没错  但不是这样的
Yeah, no.
我知道她拒绝你了  但是我想告诉你
I know that.What I wanted to say was
想要一个女朋友可不仅仅是
having a girlfriend...It's more than just
年龄相仿  兴趣相同就行的
being the same age and liking the same hockey team.
- 不仅仅是这样  - 那是怎样
- It's more than that.- Then what is it about?
对  那又怎样呢
Yeah, what is it about?
感情这种事儿啊
It's, um, it's about feeling stuff,
是要由心而发的
you know, like, on the inside.
要让互相心有灵犀
Making a connection, I guess.
让互相快乐
Making each other laugh.
能聊得开
Having conversations.
那要是很难做怎么办
What if it's hard?
聊天很难怎么办
Conversations.
相信我  这对每个人来说都不是件易事
Oh, believe me, it's hard for everybody.
不仅是对你而言
Not just you, it's...
要是有人说他们
You know, and screw the people
很容易就做得到
that it comes easy to,
这都是瞎扯淡
'cause that's not real.
听着  你看我  我也是
Look, me, I didn't have
上了大学才交女朋友的
a girlfriend until college,late college.
所以你总有一天也会交到女朋友的
The point is,it's gonna happen for you,Max.
相信我
Trust me.
向我们这样的人  要有点耐心
Guys like us,just got to take time,you know.
对这种事儿不能过于着急
Don't need to rush it.
好吗
Okay?
好吧
Okay.
我现在能继续工作了吗
Can I go back to work now?
当然行
Yeah.
谢了
Thanks.
我该做的  麦克斯
Yeah, sure thing, Max.
- 嘿  嘿  嘿  注意了  - 停会儿  有人有话要讲
- Hey, hey, hey, hey. - Here, here, here.
我想告诉你们  我们是史上最好的乐队
I also want to say,here's to the best band ever,
我们一起努力来嗨翻整个摇滚界
and let's make some rock 'n roll history.
我们还有了个乐队新成员呢
Oh, hey, we got a new honorary band mate too.
- 敬她一杯  - 干杯
- To her. - There you go!
对对对  你太棒了
Oh, yeah, yeah, no, you're so good, no.
好吧  好吧
Okay, all right.
- 哇哦   - 说真的
- Whoa. - No, but seriously,
你有天籁一般的嗓音  听起来...
you have the voice of an angel,and it's like...
- 快点  来一个  来一个  - 谢谢  太谢谢了
- Come on,hit me,hit me. - Thank you,thank you.
跟我一起唱
Sing it with me.
齐唱：我本该带你回家
Both: I should have taken you home
为什么我唱高音而你却在唱低音呢
Why are you on the bottom and I'm on the top?
好像咱俩唱反了诶
Oh, that's a nice way to slip something pervy in there.
这样不错诶
That was good.
- 这种搭配真不错  - 你们听到了吗
-That was a good combo right there-Did you hear that?
- 我喜欢这样  - 你在说什么呢
- I liked it. - What are you talking about?
别再让他喝了
Don't give him any more.
我说真的
I'm serious.
他已经喝高了
He's in trouble.
等等
Hang on.
【乐队其他成员的聊天声】
[Background chatter]
喂
Hello?
天呐  你去哪儿了
Oh, my God. Where have you been?
我给你打了一遍又一遍的电话
I've been calling and calling.
嗨  对不起  亲爱的
Hi. I'm sorry, babe,
我刚才走神了  我...
I totally spaced out, I'm...
嘿  嘿  等等  安博  安博
Hey, hey, Amber, Amber.
我们今天专辑杀青了
We finished the album today,
我们就到附近的一家酒吧
and I came around the corner,
跟乐队一起庆祝  就来玩一会而已
just to celebrate with the band,
and stuff so, just for a second,
- 我们现在庆祝完了...  - 那个...
- but we're done now... - Well-
我马上就准备回家了
and I'm gonna come right home.
我们没有看时间  所以我现在也不知道...
We didn't set a time or anything,so I didn't know
你提前下班了  所以我就一直在等你
you were getting off early,so I've been waiting.
我也提前下班了  我就在家干等着
I got off early too.I've just been waiting.
- 我很抱歉  对不起  - 不好意思
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry. - I'm sorry.
- 嘘  别闹了  - 我给你拿来了一小杯
- Shh, stop. - I got you a little one.
对不起  亲爱的  我现在正要去开车呢
I'm sorry, babe. I'm driving now, though.
- 我开车没事儿的  - 不  不  不  不行
- I'm fine to drive. - No, no, no, no, no.
- 不不不  - 安博  安博
- No, no, no, no.- Amber. Amber--
我现在就回来  住手  别闹了
I'm coming home.Shh, stop, stop, stop!
- 你不许开车  听见了吗  - 我马上就...
- Amber,you are not driving,okay?- I'm coming...
我马上来接你  好吗
I'm coming to get you, all right?
我马上就过来  别乱走
I'm coming to you.  Don't leave.
亲爱的   抱歉  我...
Babe, I'm sorry, I--
嘿  不好意思  先生
oh, hey, excuse me, sir.
- 你是麦克  对吧  - 不是  我是道格
- Mike, right? - No, Doug.
先别... 嘿  我是克罗...不好意思
No, no, hey, I'm cr--oh, sorry.
我叫克罗斯比
Crosby.
你要去吃披萨  对吗
You own pizza time, right?
- 不是  - 你不是吗
- No. - Oh, you don't?
那你是要去选举吗
Are you going to vote?
对  我现在不就是在努力吗
Yeah, I was trying.
我能问你一个简短的问题吗
Can I just ask you a quick question?
我就耽搁你一秒钟来帮我一下
I just need your guidance for one second.
你能帮我吗
Could you do me a favor?
- 行  - 好吧  谢谢你
- Yeah. - Okay, thank you.
你想投给谁呢
Who are you voting for?
小鲍
Bob Little.
别这样  小鲍吗
Oh, come on, Bob Little?
- 对  - 那个变态
- Yeah. - Guy's a pervert.
你没想过选克里斯蒂娜・布雷弗曼吗
Have you thought about Kristina Braverman?
- 哦  拜托  - 你到底不喜欢她哪点
- Oh, come on.- What don't you like about her?
什么  她见人就抱
What? She hugs everybody she meets.
她电话号码给了几乎她见过的一半人
She gets phone numbers from half the people she meets.
要是她寂寞的话  就该去约会
If she's lonely, she should go on a date.
不  她不能  因为她还有个暴力的老公
No, she can't. She got the violent husband.
对  他确实是可能有那个倾向
Yeah, he's a liability.
听我说  道格
Listen, Doug.
你有没有...可能改投克里斯蒂娜呢
Is there any way that I could sway your vote?
嘘  别这样
Shh, come on.
你在干嘛  你是想买我的选票吗
What are you doing?You trying to buy my vote?
20美元  现金哦
$20, hard cash,
卖你投给克里斯蒂娜一票
for a Kristina Braverman vote.
你觉得如何
What do you say?
好吧  听着  你真的想这么做吗
All right,look.You really want to do this?
- 对  - 那你不仅会得到一张票
- Yeah. - You're not getting one vote.
你会得到两张票
You're getting two votes.
加一张给布雷弗曼的  减去一张给小鲍的
Plus one for Braverman.Minus one for Bob Little.
帮你投一张  我自己一张  加起来就两张
Your one, plus my one is two.
两票40美元
Two votes is 40 bucks.
行  我给你40美元
Okay, I'll go 40 bucks.
- 挺合理的  - 好吧  行
- That's logical. -All right,good.
我给你40美元
I'm gonna give you the 40 bucks,
但你得给我搞一张贴纸来
but you got to get me a sticker.
- 成交  - 好吧
- Done. - All right.
别忘了贴纸  布雷弗曼的
Don't forget the sticker.Braverman.
要是你向他们要的话  他们也会给你的
They'll give you a sticker if you just ask them.
嘘  天呐
Shh, jeez.
? 澡堂子里最漂亮的姑娘
? The prettiest girl in this bathroom
你进球了
Oh, you got it!
你进...嘿
You got the--hey.
你想跟我斗舞吗
You want to come make the dance happen?
来吧  来吧
Bring it. Bring it.
我可不怕你
I'm not scared.
我才不怕...
I'm not scared--
等等  什么
wait, what, what, what, what?
我知道怎么回事儿了
I know what's happening.
你觉得要把罗马着这头
Okay,so what do you think the over-under is
美洲豹给弄回去得怎样做
on Rome taking cougar home?
太恶心了
That's disgusting.
你还好吗
You all right?
我跟瑞恩闹矛盾了
I just got into a thing with Ryan,and--
而且都是我的错
it's my fault.
我本来给回去陪他的  我...
I was supposed to hang out with him,and I--
现在我感觉糟透了  因为我搞砸了
I don't know,I feel really bad,'cause I messed up.
听着  我觉得这可能不是你的错
Look,I think that it's probably not your fault.
你在跟乐队一起录专辑
You're recording on an album with a band.
你会玩的非常开心的
You're gonna have a good time and hang out.
我本来以为
I thought it was gonna be,
我们就喝一两杯就散  结果却...
like,one drink,and then it turned into--
你们俩亲热完了告诉我一声  我们好会去
when you guys are done cuddling, we can go.
嘿  嘿  不是你想的那样  我们走吧
Hey, hey, it's not that.Let's go.
- 你准备好了吗   - 你还好吗
- You ready? - Are you okay?
她好得很  把你的手拿开  老兄
She's fine.Take your hands off her,dude.
- 嘿  嘿  嘿  - 嘿  冷静点  冷静
- Hey,hey,hey,hey.- Hey,hey,chill,chill.
这家伙再找你们麻烦吗
Is this guy giving you trouble?
奥利弗  住手  住手  没事儿的
Oliver, stop, stop, stop. It's fine.
嘿  嘿
Hey, hey--
嘿嘿嘿  放开他
hey, hey, hey! Let go of him!
- 瑞恩  放开他  - 哇哦  冷静点
- Ryan,let go of him. - Whoa,whoa,chill out,hey.
嘿  瑞恩  不要
Hey! Ryan, no.
住手  瑞恩
Stop! Ryan.
瑞恩  瑞恩  快给我住手
Ryan! Ryan, stop it right now!
放开他  求你了  瑞恩
Get off of him, Ryan, please.
瑞恩・约克  快给我放开他
Ryan York, get off of him now!
嗨  宝贝
Hi, sweetheart.
哦~  安博  哦~  宝贝
Oh, Amber.Oh, honey.
对不起
Sorry.
哦~  宝贝
Oh, sweetheart.
好了  好了  没事了  别哭了
No, it's okay, come on.
不哭  不哭  不哭啊  宝贝
No, no, no, no, no. Come on, sweetheart.
别哭了  外公在呢
It's all right. I'm here.
我觉得就是想好了
Plotting and planning left and right.
在图纸上画上几笔
I guess.
【狂笑中】
[Laughter]
我知道德鲁会会有你这样一个
I knew drew was gonna have this, like,
又年轻又漂亮的老妈
cool, hip, young, pretty mom.
- 哇哦   好吧  - 德鲁知道吗
- Wow. Okay...- Does drew know?
- 我一会再给你钱  - 那就快给吧
- I'll give you the money later.- Oh,please do.
对  你欠我的
Yeah, you owe me for that.
你们俩那个多久了  你懂的
How long have you guys--you know?
我们只是朋友而已
Oh, no, we're just friends.
- 就是这样  - 哦
- Yeah. - Oh.
- 普通朋友而已  - 哦
- It's casual. - Oh.
- 非常普通  - 对
- Very casual. - Yeah.
普通朋友  对  当然的啦
Casual, yeah, sure.
那就继续普通下去吧
Keeping it casual.
百分之八十的选票已经被统计出来了
80% of votes have been counted,
我们领先了七千票
and we're 7,000 votes ahead.
- 不错嘛  - 太棒了
- Good. - Great.
但是小鲍的选区票数还没统计出来
But Bob Little's districts haven't come in yet.
- 哦  - 你是谁
- Oh. - Who are you?
这是娜塔莉  她是我的...
This is Natalie. She's my--
你们是男女朋友关系吗
are you boyfriend and girlfriend?
- 不  我们就是朋友而已  - 嗯  不是
- No, we're just friends. - Um, no.
我才邀请我的第一个女孩一起约会呢
I just asked my first girl out.
- 不错  做得好  - 不错
- Nice! Good work. - Nice.
- 但是她拒绝了我  - 那是她的损失
- But then she said no.- Well, her loss.
- 她住在明尼苏达  - 对
- She lives in Minnesota anyway.- Yeah.
但很明显异地恋太糟糕了
And apparently long-distance relationships are hell.
确实是
That's true.
好吧  待会儿再聊
All right.Talk to you later.
我没觉得有什么问题啊
I don't see what the problem is.
你买了张选票
You bought a vote?
你说得没错  我买了张选票
You're damn right, I bought a vote.
要是她一票的优势获胜
If she wins by one vote,
这将会是我花过最有价值的40美元
that's gonna be the best $40 dollars I ever spent.
你不能那样做
You can't do that.
你又怎么知道他原先不是打算投给克里斯蒂娜的呢
How are you so sure he even voted for Kristina?
- 你什么时候变得那么喜欢挖苦人了  - 你不能买选票
- When did you become such a cynic? - You can't buy a vote.
我看过那家伙的眼睛  他值得我信任
I saw in this man's eyes he was a trustworthy man.
- 真的吗  - 天呐
- Oh, really? - Oh, my goodness.
他卖了自己的选票
I mean, he sold his vote,
但他值得信任  就是这样
but he was very trustworthy,other than that.
我们的谈一谈
We need to talk.
我甚至敢把艾达托付给他
I would have trusted him with Aida--
- 嘿  乔  - 嘿  大家好
- hey, Joel.- Hey, guys.
- 你还好吗  - 去去就回
- How's it going? - We'll be right back.
那个三明治是几号
What number sandwich is that?
三根手指意味着是五号
Three means five, doesn't it?
我一直在努力处理维克多的事儿
I was trying to deal with Victor,
他最近一直很沮丧
and he's so upset.
- 嗯  - 他非常沮丧  而且...
- Yes. - He is so upset and--
这不是你想扮演的角色吗
that's the position you wanted to be in.
我感觉你没有关心他
I feel like you're not there.
我没有关心维克多吗
I'm not there for Victor?
我感觉你根本一点都不顾家
I feel like you're not even there.
我很关心他  也很关心西德妮
I am there for him.I am there for Sydney.
你到底想干嘛
What more do you want?
那我呢  我现在需要你
What about me?I needed you in that moment.
- 你吗  - 我觉得我快被淹死了
- What about you?- I felt like I was drowning,
而且我还抓不到你的手
and I could not get a hold of you,
而你却随随便便地吃着寿司晚餐
and you're just having casual sushi dinner.
你怎么能这样对我
How could you do that to me?
- 你怎么能这样对我  - 我不知道...
- How could you do that to me?- I don't know...
我根本就感觉不到你
I could not get a hold of you.
我从不会闯进你在莱昂・邓格拉夫
I never would have walked into your office
公司的办公室  也不会跟他那样讲话
with Leon Dengraff and talked to him that way.
我从不会对他这样做
I never would have done that to him.
我也从没有这样对你过
I never would have done that to you.
乔  这无关乎于工作
Joel,this is not about the work.
我绝对不会这样对他
I never would have treated him that way.
也绝不会这样对你
I never would have treated you that way.
那样可能会害我丢掉饭碗的  茱莉亚
That could have cost me my job,Julia.
- 乔  这是关于...  - 九年了
- Joel, this is about...- Nine years.
- 我给了你九年时间   - 维克多
- I give you nine years. - Victor.
我拥护了你九年
I championed you for nine years,
而你却不肯给我...
and you can't give me--
连三个月都不肯给我吗
you can't give me three months.
这与工作无关
This is not about the work.
无关吗
It's not?
这是关于我们家现在爆发的家庭危机
This is about a family crisis that is happening right now.
你工作的时候就跟工作有关
It was about the work when you were working.
It was about the work when you were working,
而我就一直默默在你背后支持着你
and I was there for you.I supported you.
当时我们也没遇到过现在这种事啊
We never went through anything like this.
我一直看着你所做的证词
I looked over every deposition you had.
我一直拥护着你的每一次尝试  每一次啊 茱莉亚
I was there to champion every trial, every trial, Julia.
我也跟你一起在分享着这个项目的喜悦  乔
I'm sharing in your joy on this project,Joel.
好极了  还真是表现出来了
Great, it really shows.
但我们正经历着家庭危机
But we're going through a family crisis right now.
好吧  好吧
Okay, okay, well--
而我觉得你根本就不关心
and I feel like you're not there.
我会去关心的
Well, I'll be there.
我马上就去解决这事儿
I'll go solve it right now.
告诉克里斯蒂娜我很抱歉不能在这儿陪你
Tell Kristina I'm sorry I couldn't be here for you
也不能陪我们的孩子
and there for our children.
天呐
God.
好吧  最新战况如何
Okay, so what is the latest?
我们得挺住了
You know,we're hanging in there.
我们有一点落后
You know, we're down a bit,
- 但票数非常接近  所以...  - 好吧
- but it's close, so... - Okay.
就看四区的情况如何了
Just waiting for district four to come in.
四区可是小鲍的王国啊
District four,that's Bob little country.
对  但是最近你的支持率在那边也有所上升
Yeah,but your numbers have been getting better there.
四区什么时候才会弄完
When do we expect the districtfour numbers to come in?
随时都有可能
You know, any minute.
- 准备好你的演讲吗  - 当然准备好了
- You got your speeches? - Yes, I do.
不论胜败  都准备好了
I've got the winning and I've got the losing.
海瑟  你的本能告诉你了什么
Heather, what does your gut tell you?
我的本能告诉我  胜利在即
You know,my gut tells me that it's close.
那样说对我也没什么帮助现在
Well, that is not helping me right now.
好吧  听着 克里斯蒂娜  去豪饮两杯
All right, look, Kristina,get some booze.
这样会让你冷静点
You know, it'll calm your nerves.
反正不管如何你都得要喝的
You're gonna need it either way.
听着  不论结果如何  你都做得非常棒
And, look, hey, either way, you did great.
真的
Really.
- 我们要输了  - 嘿  别这样想
- We're gonna lose. - Hey.
你刚才没看到她的表情吗
Did you see that look on her face?
亲爱的  我们输定了
Honey, we're going down.
我觉着她可能是有点消化不良而已
I just think--I think she has a little indigestion.
好吗
All right?
别想太多  好吗
Don't read too much into this stuff, okay?
- 我实在是太紧张了  - 我知道
- I'm just nervous. - I know.
我去给你弄杯喝的  好吗
Let me get you that drink, all right?
好吧  亲爱的
Okay, honey?
嗯
Mm.
好吗
Okay?
谢谢  谢谢
Thank you.Thank you.
非常感谢
Thank you all so very much.
我刚才接到小鲍的电话
I just got off the phone with Bob Little,
我没能赢他
and I conceded the election to him.
我失败了
It's a bummer.
票数非常接近了  但他确实竞选得非常棒
It was very close, but he ran a great race,
我觉得他一定会成为一个非常优秀的市长的
and I think that Bob is going to make an incredible mayor.
我想借此机会感谢各位
I just want to take this opportunity to say thank you
感谢你们在这整场竞选中
so much all of you that have supported me
这么支持我
throughout this campaign,
我是打心底感激你们
and I mean that from the bottom of my heart.
你们中或许有人不知道
You know,some of you might not know this,
一年之前
but a year ago,
我从未想过会站在这个舞台
I thought I might not even be here today,
我这样说一点也没有夸大其词
and I'm not exaggerating when I say that.
我真没有预料到事情会朝什么方向发展
I really didn't know which way things were going to turn out.
我只想告诉你们
And I just want to say how grateful
我能在这儿有多感激大家
I am that I actually am here,and with
有了你们的帮助  我才能实现
your help I'm able to fulfill a dream of mine
我曾经连想都不敢想的事儿
that I never thought possible.
我只想感谢你们所有的人
All of you, I just thank you,
而且我真的还想继续与你们保持联系
and I really want to stay in touch with you.
你们大部分人都有我的电话号码
Most of you have my cell phone number...
这样很好
Which is good.
祝你们今晚玩得愉快
Have a wonderful night,
我爱你们大家
and I love you all.
非常感谢
Thank you.
【欢呼与鼓掌声】
[Cheers and applause]
做得好
Good job.
嗨
Hi.
我真为你骄傲
I'm proud of you.
你做到了
You kicked butt.
嗨  我是辩论赛上那个卡洛琳・李
Hi, it's Caroline Lee from the debate.
- 你还好吗  - 很好
- How are you? - Good.
能见到你真是太高兴了
So nice to see you.
很高兴见到你
Nice to see you,
这是我的女儿 艾玛
and this is my daughter, Emma,
她想告诉你一些事
and she wants to tell you something.
好啊
Yeah.
她说：“因为你  我才转到了”
She says, "because of you I've moved to a better school
“一个更好的学校  更好的班级”
"and a better classroom
“才有那么多人一起帮助我学习”
with people who are helping me to learn."
她说：“谢谢你改变了我的人生”
She says "thank you for changing my life,"
也改变了我的人生
and mine.
你们也改变了我的人生
Oh, you've just changed mine.
这比世上其它任何事
That means more to me than anything
都对我有意义  谢谢你  艾玛
in the whole world.Thank you, Emma.
我能抱抱你吗
Can I give you a hug?
当然可以
Definitely.
? 让你欢乐  宝贝
? Joy to you, baby
? 让我今夜如此欢乐
? joy to me too tonight
? 今夜  今夜
? tonight, tonight
谢谢观看  更多字幕请关注“幕雨字幕组”新浪微博